At
Could you give me a Triple Combo first?
Ah～ You want to freeload?!!!
Then how about giving a free like～
Hello everyone
I'm Baichuan.
So starting from today
We will guide you through the basics of DEFI
to a DEFI project hands-on
Then the emergence of DEFA means that even if you're not a technical person
can also participate in the definition of AI
or we develop an AI application product ourselves
Since AI has many built-in models,
our current models
basically, there is support for all of these on the DEFI platform.
We can intuitively invoke this model
or intuitively orchestrate our corresponding large models
For example, some of our RAG applications
or our corresponding agent
can all be implemented on DEFI
Then, DEFI actually for us
Why do we use DEFI?
Actually, we previously had options like Kouzi as well
or when we previously developed this large model
what is commonly referred to as such a framework
Then this type of development framework
For example, we have some tools that
We can do more customized development
this DEFI
can more quickly or more intuitively see the results of their own project
what the outcome looks like
Then we can integrate through this large model
existing business operations
can help you quickly build
this AI Knowledge system
so you don’t need to waste a lot of my time
So with DEFI now,
allows everyone to utilize large model applications
as well as our development at the application layer
so that everyone can use it more conveniently
Next, let's take a look at how to set up DEFI
perform a private deployment
First, let's take a look at the official website address for the deployment method
This is the official website of DEFI.
This is an open-source address on GitHub.
First of all, before using DEFADE,
We need to prepare the corresponding Docker.
For this Docker, you can use it on a server,
You can use either Windows or Mac.
Here I am using the one on Windows
There's nothing here yet.
Currently, there's nothing in this empty Docker.
Then inside the Docker,
When installing Windows, there are a few things we need to pay attention to
we need to enable its virtualization service
There are no other particularly special points.
Then what do we need to do
In Docker, we also need to configure its origin address.
This origin is because it uses a foreign source.
We'll change it to a domestic domestic source address
Otherwise, the download speed will be extremely slow.
You'll also have this thing inside.
Just add this part and it will be fine
Okay, just click save and restart then. Alright?
Well, there's nothing else particularly special.
Then it's just about our CPU
and our RAM
Please pay attention
Apart from this,
We need to get its source code
The way to obtain it is
that is, here we are
You can download the version you want.
Here I downloaded a ZIP file
I downloaded version 1.11.212 of the software, okay
After downloading, proceed to extract the files
After decompression, you can see a file like this, right?
Now that we have this software,
For example, we can place it
I habitually place it in our corresponding D drive.
place it in our software drive
Alright, once we have it
How can we load this code
The loading method is actually quite simple.
Let's show you
So the logic is very simple
For example, if we want to load DEFI
First, inside your compressed file
Enter your corresponding folder
Then what will be inside it
there will be one called define uh
This Docker goes into the DDOCKER folder
Then inside the docker,
version changed
Because this is our corresponding configuration file
is what we need among many
or in some of our projects
Need to load some environments or something
or some of our configuration information
actually in this UNV
Then we proceed to execute the second piece of code
Load our corresponding configurations through Docker
It will locate our corresponding YM file.
configured YM file
then download his file package
The execution method is also quite simple.
It means we are in the current file directory CD um
install via Docker
I won't go into these details
Because there's nothing particularly special about it.
Okay
Executed
Then here
Here, many software packages will be installed.
some dependencies of our DEFI
for example, during deployment, right
such as NGINX
as well as services like REDIS
like our corresponding API services
as well as some other tools of ours
The download here will take some time
Then if you are using a foreign language here
it may fail to download
That's why we just had you configure
domestic language
The download speed will be very fast.
It will take some time here
Let's let it run first, okay
While it's running
Let's take a closer look, okay
Then there is actually information contained in this file.
please pay more attention to it
In fact, the ENV stores
those configuration contents and data
This indicates that we need to load some
such as database or DB
and some configurations like Redis
all here
Like this MySQL configuration information
Not this, not MySQL
Then, regarding our corresponding configuration contents
Here in this section, and also, we have one below
Is there this file
Ah, this is where the packages we need will be stored.
the address where some packages were downloaded
where to download from
Then let's take a look
It is actually in this command
He has already got the software up and running
the application has already been launched
So we can directly open our URL to access it.
Ah, now running
and then we can see that your have run some
some downloaded images
These are the images we have downloaded
Then after it's up and running, let's take a look inside the container, okay
Now the corresponding content has been successfully loaded
the content is up and running
Okay, the container is running smoothly.
So how do we access it next?
The access method is actually quite simple
You can directly access the corresponding server
because we have downloaded an NGINX
You can directly access it locally.